Boston Streets Collection MS102
Tufts Archival Research Center
Boston Streets Collection
1848 -- 1960
1762 -- 1980
Tufts Archival Research Center
Digital Collections and Archives
MS102
3216 Digital Object(s)
Arrangement
This collection is organized into three series: Images, unbound; Boston City Directories; Maps and atlases of Boston.
Scope and Contents
This collection contains the digital content collected and created for use in the Boston Streets project. Boston Streets: Mapping Directory data was developed by the Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University, with support from a National Leadership Grant from the Institute of Museum and Library Services. Additional support was provided by Docema, The Bostonian Society, and other anonymous gifts. The Bostonian Society provided more than 3000 images to the project and was also a major partner in developing descriptive cataloging specifications. The collection is comprised of images, maps, and street directories from the years 1762 -- 1980. To view the Boston Streets digital exhibit, please see:
Biographical / Historical
Tufts Archival Research Center is the Tufts University steward for all archival records and materials of significant and historical relevance to the college.
The collection began as the University Archives, which were incorporated in 1965 by the Tufts University Board of Trustees (Annual Reports 1965-1988). Previously, the position of archivist was loosely created in 1959 as a means of processing and acquiring important university and student records for preservation. This role was filled by Tufts history professor and historian Russell L. Miller, who also wrote the Tufts University history "Light on the Hill." The archives were considered a department of the University Library (known as Eaton and then Wessell at that time), overseen by the College of Arts, Sciences and Engineering.
The university's archives were first kept in Eaton Library, but moved to the Wessell Library building in 1965. Originals of some records were sent to vaults in Ballou Hall for storage. In 1991, due to budget issues, the university archivist was laid off. When the office was reopened in 1997, it was as the University Archives and Special Collections, also located as a department within the Tisch Library.
In July 2001, Digital Collections and Archives (DCA) was created when the University Archives was tasked with developing a Tufts Digital Library. The department moved from the College of Arts, Science and Engineering to the Central Administration, directed by the University Provost. The Special Collections department remained under Tisch Library.
In January 2023, DCA was renamed Tufts Archival Research Center (TARC) to better reflect the mission and services offered by the department.
TARC is currently physically housed in the Tisch Library building.
Conditions Governing Access
This collection is open for research.
Boston (Mass.); Boston(Mass.)-Directories; Boston (Mass.) - Maps.
- Images, unbound, 1762 -- 1980; MS102.001; 409 Digital Object(s)
  Scope and Contents
  This series contains digital manifestations of photographs of Boston from The Bostonian Society and the Tufts University Archives.
  Arrangement
  This series is arranged geographically by street name.
  Conditions Governing Access
  Open for research.
  - Adams Square, 1950; MS102.001.DO.00001; Unknown
    Date is approximate
    Massachusetts; Boston (Mass.); Adams Square; Brattle Street; Washington Street; Devonshire Street; Buildings; Social and civic buildings; Faneuil Hall; Public buildings; Government buildings; Commercial buildings; Custom House; Squares (open spaces); Statues; Towers; Clock-towers; Automobiles; Pedestrians; Adams, Samuel
  - Dock Square, 1920; MS102.001.DO.00002; Unknown
    Massachusetts; Boston (Mass.); Dock Square; Washington Street; Elm Street; Faneuil Hall Square; Devonshire Street; Buildings; Commercial buildings; Businesses; Restaurants, lunch rooms, etc.; Stores, retail; Shoe stores; Tailor shops; Automobiles; Trucks; Railroad tracks; Pedestrians; Adams Square Counter Lunch; Central Building Wrecking Company; Diamond-Union Stamp Works; Cagan and Copperstein Custom Pants Makers; C.L. Tailors, Inc.; Dock Square Shoe Repairing Company; Aschulte Cigars; Patten's Restaurant; Boston Elevated Railway
  - Asher Benjamin House and the Earle Hotel, July, 1961-07-01; MS102.001.DO.00003; Unknown
    Massachusetts; Boston (Mass.); Beacon Hill (Mass.); Allston Street; Buildings; Houses; Hotels; Earle Hotel; Asher Benjamin House; Benjamin, Asher; Earle Hotel
  - Asher Benjamin House on Allston Street, July, 1961-07-01; MS102.001.DO.00004; Unknown
    Massachusetts; Boston (Mass.); Beacon Hill (Mass.); Allston Street; Buildings; Dwellings; Houses; Automobiles; Decoration and ornament, Architectural; Hand-railing; Automobiles; Benjamin, Asher
  - House on Allston Street, 1961-05-30; MS102.001.DO.00005; Unknown
    Massachusetts; Boston (Mass.); Beacon Hill (Mass.); Allston Street; Buildings; Dwellings; Houses
  - A house on Allston Street, July, 1961-07-01; MS102.001.DO.00006; Unknown
    Massachusetts; Boston (Mass.); Beacon Hill (Mass.); Allston Street; Buildings; Dwellings; Houses; Apartment houses
  - 11-23 Allston Street, n.d., MS102.001.DO.00007; Unknown
    Massachusetts; Boston (Mass.); Beacon Hill (Mass.); Allston Street; Buildings; Dwellings; Houses; Laborers; Street lights
  - Massachusetts State House from Bowdoin and Derne Streets, 1928; MS102.001.DO.00010; Unknown
    Massachusetts; Boston (Mass.); Beacon Hill (Mass.); Bowdoin Street; Derne Street; Buildings; Public buildings; Government buildings; Capitols; Massachusetts State House; Statues; Bulfinch Commemorative Column to American Independence; Automobiles
  - Work site on the grounds of the Massachusetts State House, 1900; MS102.001.DO.00011; Unknown
    Massachusetts; Boston (Mass.); Beacon Hill (Mass.); Bowdoin Street; Derne Street; Buildings; Public buildings; Government buildings; Capitols; Massachusetts State House; Parks; Horses; Wagons; Building sites; Pedestrians
  - Dedication of the statue of Daniel Webster before the Massachusetts State House, 1859-09-07; MS102.001.DO.00012; Unknown
    Massachusetts; Boston (Mass.); Beacon Hill (Mass.); Beacon Street; Bowdoin Street; Park Street; Buildings; Public buildings; Government buildings; Capitols; Massachusetts State House; Houses; Spires; People; Webster, Daniel
  - Massachusetts State House, 1865; MS102.001.DO.00013; Hawes, Josiah Johnson
    Massachusetts; Boston (Mass.); Beacon Hill (Mass.); Beacon Street; Hancock Place; Buildings; Government buildings; Public buildings; Capitols; Massachusetts State House; Dwellings; Houses; Horse-drawn vehicles; Wagons; People; Men; Webster, Daniel; Mann, Horace
  - Massachusetts State House illuminated for Christmas, 1932; MS102.001.DO.00014; Unknown
    Massachusetts; Boston (Mass.); Beacon Hill (Mass.); Beacon Street; Buildings; Public buildings; Government buildings; Capitols; Massachusetts State House; Statues; Festive decorations; Webster, Daniel; Mann, Horace
  - View of the Massachusetts State House from Boston Common, 1920-10-26; MS102.001.DO.00015; Belcher, Arnold L.
    Massachusetts; Boston (Mass.); Beacon Hill (Mass.); Beacon Street; Buildings; Public buildings; Government buildings; Capitols; Massachusetts State House; People
  - Massachusetts State House, 1860 -- 1880; MS102.001.DO.00016; Unknown
    Massachusetts; Boston (Mass.); Beacon Hill (Mass.); Beacon Street; Buildings; Public buildings; Government buildings; Massachusetts State House; Statues; Fountains; Mann, Horace; Webster, Daniel
  - Massachusetts State House, n.d., MS102.001.DO.00017; Unknown
    Massachusetts; Boston (Mass.); Beacon Hill (Mass.); Beacon Street; Buildings; Public buildings; Government buildings; Capitols; Massachusetts State House; Awnings; Parks; Commons; Boston Common
  - Massachusetts State House, 1856 -- 1889; MS102.001.DO.00018; Ward, Joseph and Son
    Massachusetts; Boston (Mass.); Beacon Hill (Mass.); Beacon Street; Park Street; Buildings; Public buildings; Government buildings; Capitols; Massachusetts State House; Statues; Fountains; Webster, Daniel
  - Massachusetts State House, 1856 -- 1889; MS102.001.DO.00019; Ward, Joseph and Son
    Massachusetts; Boston (Mass.); Beacon Hill (Mass.); Beacon Street; Park Street; Buildings; Public buildings; Government buildings; Capitols; Massachusetts State House; Statues; Fountains; Mann, Horace; Webster, Daniel
  - Massachusetts State House, 1856 -- 1889; MS102.001.DO.00020; Unknown
    Massachusetts; Boston (Mass.); Beacon Hill (Mass.); Beacon Street; Buildings; Public buildings; Government buildings; Capitols; Massachusetts State House; Statues; Fountains; Webster, Daniel
  - Massachusetts State House, 1856 -- 1889; MS102.001.DO.00021; Unknown
  - Massachusetts State House, 1856 -- 1889; MS102.001.DO.00022; Unknown
  - Massachusetts State House, 1930; MS102.001.DO.00023; Unknown
    Massachusetts; Boston (Mass.); Beacon Hill (Mass.); Beacon Street; Buildings; Public buildings; Government buildings; Capitols; Massachusetts State House; Statues; Scaffolding; Mann, Horace; Webster, Daniel
  - Massachusetts State House, 1931; MS102.001.DO.00024; Unknown
    Massachusetts; Boston (Mass.); Beacon Hill (Mass.); Beacon Street; Boston Common; Buildings; Public buildings; Government buildings; Capitols; Massachusetts State House; Automobiles; People; Children; Boys
  - Massachusetts State House at night, 1930; MS102.001.DO.00025; Unknown
    Massachusetts; Boston (Mass.); Beacon Hill (Mass.); Boston Common; Beacon Street; Buildings; Public buildings; Government buildings; Capitols; Massachusetts State House; Commons; Boston Common; Trees; Street lights
  - Massachusetts State House during a fireworks display, 1930; MS102.001.DO.00026; Unknown
    Massachusetts; Boston (Mass.); Beacon Hill (Mass.); Boston Common; Beacon Street; Buildings; Public buildings; Government buildings; Capitols; Massachusetts State House; Commons; Boston Common; Fireworks
  - Massachusetts State House, 1954; MS102.001.DO.00027; Woodman, W.C.
    Massachusetts; Boston (Mass.); Beacon Hill (Mass.); Beacon Street; Buildings; Public buildings; Government buildings; Capitols; Massachusetts State House; Statues; Flags; Flagpoles; Mann, Horace; Webster, Daniel
  - Massachusetts State House and surrounding Beacon Hill area after a blizzard, 1940-02-18; MS102.001.DO.00028; Snow, Edward R.
    Massachusetts; Boston (Mass.); Beacon Hill (Mass.); Boston Common; Beacon Street; Tremont Street; Joy Street; Buildings; Public buildings; Government buildings; Capitols; Massachusetts State House; Dwellings; Parks; Commons; Boston Common; Snow
  - Massachusetts State House, 1890; MS102.001.DO.00029; Unknown
    Massachusetts; Boston (Mass.); Beacon Hill (Mass.); Beacon Street; Buildings; Public buildings; Government buildings; Capitols; Massachusetts State House; Statues; Fountains; Gates; Pedestrians; Women; Signs and signboards; Mann, Horace; Webster, Daniel
  - Massachusetts State House, 1856 -- 1889; MS102.001.DO.00030; Unknown
    Massachusetts; Boston (Mass.); Beacon Hill (Mass.); Park Street; Beacon Street; Buildings; Public buildings; Government buildings; Capitols; Massachusetts State House; Dwellings; Houses; Street lights; Awnings
  - Hancock House at 30 Beacon Street, 1830 -- 1860; MS102.001.DO.00031; Unknown
    Massachusetts; Boston (Mass.); Beacon Hill (Mass.); Beacon Street; Buildings; Dwellings; Houses; Fences; Trees; People; Women
  - Statue of Anne Marbury Hutchinson, n.d., MS102.001.DO.00032; Unknown
    Massachusetts; Boston (Mass.); Beacon Hill (Mass.); Statues; Hutchinson, Anne Marbury
  - Detail of the Massachusetts State House dome and lantern, n.d., MS102.001.DO.00033; Unknown
    Massachusetts; Boston (Mass.); Beacon Hill (Mass.); Beacon Street; Buildings; Public buildings; Government buildings; Capitols; Massachusetts State House; Domes; Lanterns; Statues
  - Massachusetts State House, 1895 -- 1914; MS102.001.DO.00034; Unknown
    Massachusetts; Boston (Mass.); Beacon Hill (Mass.); Hancock Avenue; Park Street; Beacon Street; Buildings; Public buildings; Government buildings; Capitols; Massachusetts State House; Houses; Statues; Fountains; People; Mann, Horace; Webster, Daniel
  - Military parade before the Massachusetts State House, 1930; MS102.001.DO.00035; Unknown
    Massachusetts; Boston (Mass.); Beacon Hill (Mass.); Beacon Street; Buildings; Public buildings; Government buildings; Capitols; Massachusetts State House; People; Soldiers; Military parades and ceremonies
  - Massachusetts State House, 1895; MS102.001.DO.00036; Unknown
    Massachusetts; Boston (Mass.); Beacon Hill (Mass.); Beacon Street; Bowdoin Street; Buildings; Public buildings; Government buildings; Capitols; Massachusetts State House; Statues; People; Webster, Daniel; Hooker, Major-General Joseph Fighting Joe
  - Odd Fellows Hall, 1880; MS102.001.DO.00037; Unknown
    Massachusetts; Boston (Mass.); South End (Mass.); Tremont Street; Warren Avenue; Berkeley Street; Buildings; Commercial buildings; Social and civic buildings; Fraternal orgnaizations; Libraries; Willcox and Gibbs Sewing Machine Company
  - Symphony, Horticultural and Chickering Halls, n.d., MS102.001.DO.00038; Unknown
    Massachusetts; Boston (Mass.); Huntington Avenue; Buildings; Concert halls; Music halls; Trolley buses-tracks
  - Pemberton Square, September, 1885-09-01; MS102.001.DO.00039; Wilcox, J. A. J.
    Pemberton Square; Tremont Street; Court Street; Somerset Street; Squares (open spaces); Parks; Buildings; Dwellings; Houses; Awnings; Commercial buildings; Horse-drawn vehicles; People; Bicycles
  - Bromfield House, 1858; MS102.001.DO.00040; Unknown
    Massachusetts; Boston (Mass.); Bromfield Street; Buildings; Commercial buildings; Apartment houses; Horse-drawn vehicles; Signs and signboards; Street-lighting; Churches; People; Men; Women; Crockett, S. Frank; Bromfield House; Second Methodist Episcopal Church
  - Tremont Street Methodist Episcopal Church, 1862 -- 1875; MS102.001.DO.00041; Ward, Joseph and Son
    Massachusetts; Boston (Mass.); Back Bay (Mass.); South Boston (Mass.); Tremont Street; Worcester Street; Buildings; Churches; Steeples; Clocks and watches; Tremont Street Methodist Episcopal Church
  - Chickering Hall at 239 Huntington Avenue, n.d., MS102.001.DO.00042; Unknown
    Massachusetts; Boston (Mass.); Huntington Avenue; Buildings; Concert halls; Music halls; Chickering & Sons
  - Boston Elevated Railway Removal, 411 - 617 Atlantic Avenue, 1942; MS102.001.DO.00043; International News Photos, Inc., Boston
    Massachusetts; Boston (Mass.); Atlantic Avenue; Summer Street; Northern Avenue; People; Automobiles; Commercial vehicles; Railroads, construction; Harbor Building; Russia Building; Elevated railroads; Gulf; Jedco Tavern Bar; Craftsman Machinery Co.; C.H. Batchelder Co. (flags and awnings); Boston Elevated Railway
  - Boston Elevated Railway removal, 411 - 617 Atlantic Avenue, 1942; MS102.001.DO.00044; International News Photos, Inc., Boston
    Massachusetts; Boston (Mass.); Atlantic Avenue; Northern Avenue; People; Automobiles; Commercial buildings; Harbor Building; Russia Building; Elevated railroads; Jedco Tavern Bar; Craftsman Machinery Co.; Gulf; Boston Elevated Railway
  - 450-500 Atlantic Avenue at the corner of Pearl Street, MS102.001.DO.00045; Unknown
    Massachusetts; Boston (Mass.); Atlantic Avenue; Pearl Street; Roads--Boston and vicinity; Buildings; Roads
  - South Station, corner of Atlantic Avenue and Summer Street, 1900; MS102.001.DO.00046; Unknown
    Massachusetts; Boston (Mass.); Dewey Square; Atlantic Avenue; Summer Street; Electric railway cars; Railroad terminals; Horse-drawn vehicles; People; South Station; Boston Elevated Railway
  - South Station at Dewey Square, 1900; MS102.001.DO.00047; Unknown
    Massachusetts; Boston (Mass.); Dewey Square; Electric railway cars; Horse-drawn vehicles; People; Railroad terminals; South Station
  - Atlantic Avenue at Broad Street, 1930; MS102.001.DO.00048; Unknown
    Massachusetts; Boston (Mass.); Atlantic Avenue; Rowes Wharf; Railroads, elevated; Commercial vehicles; People; Gorham Fire Equipment Co.; Boston Elevated Railway; C.W. Mitchell (drug store)
  - Boston Elevated Railway Removal, Atlantic Avenue, 1942; MS102.001.DO.00049; International News Photos, Inc., Boston
    Massachusetts; Boston (Mass.); Dewey Square; Atlantic Avenue; Railroads, elevated; Railroad terminals; Automobiles; Commercial vehicles; Awnings; Boston Elevated Railway; Hotel Essex; Walton Shoe
  - South Station, Atlantic Avenue and Summer Street, 1960 -- 1980; MS102.001.DO.00050; Unknown
    Massachusetts; Boston (Mass.); Dewey Square; Atlantic Avenue; Summer Street; Railroad terminals; South Station
  - Boston Elevated Railway, Atlantic Avenue and Summer Street, 1942., MS102.001.DO.00051; International News Photos, Inc., Boston
    Massachusetts; Boston (Mass.); Dewey Square; Atlantic Avenue; Summer Street; Railroad terminals; Commercial vehicles; People; Automobiles; Boston Elevated Railway
  - Boston Elevated Railway, Atlantic Avenue at Beach Street, 1942; MS102.001.DO.00052; International News Photos, Inc., Boston
    Massachusetts; Atlantic Avenue; Beach Street; Railroads, elevated; Boston Elevated Railway
  - 388-400 Atlantic Avenue, rear, 1947; MS102.001.DO.00053; Dennis, J.K.
    Massachusetts; Atlantic Avenue; Commercial vehicles; Automobiles; H.G. Cox Lobster Co.
  - 388-400 Atlantic Avenue, 1947; MS102.001.DO.00054; Dennis, J.K.
    Massachusetts; Boston (Mass.); Atlantic Avenue; Commercial buildings; Automobiles; Stores, retail; Marine Hardware + Supply Company; Colmar Belting Co.; Atlantic Tavern; H.G. Cox Lobster Co.
  - 388-400 Atlantic Avenue from Boston Harbor, 1947; MS102.001.DO.00055; Dennis, J.K.
    Massachusetts; Boston (Mass.); Atlantic Avenue; Foster's Wharf; Boston Harbor; Commercial buildings
  - Fire fighters and police repond to a rubbish fire at 29 Auburn Street, December 4, 1952-12-04; MS102.001.DO.00056; Boston Housing Authority
    Massachusetts; Boston (Mass.); West End (Mass.); Auburn Street; Chambers Street; Buildings; Dwellings; Houses; Commercial buildings; Businesses; Automobiles; Trucks, automobile; People; Police; Firemen; Grocers; Boston Fire Department; Boston Police Department
  - Avon Place from the corner of Washington Street, 1855; MS102.001.DO.00057; Unknown
    Massachusetts; Boston (Mass.); Avon Place; Washington Street; Buildings; Dwellings; Houses; Commercial buildings; Businesses; Horse-drawn vehicles; Wagons; Street-lighting
  - Panorama of Back Bay northeast toward Boston Common, 1880; MS102.001.DO.00058; Unknown
    Massachusetts; Boston (Mass.); Back Bay (Mass.); Newbury Street; Commonwealth Avenue; Boylston Street; Buildings; Dwellings; Houses; Churches; Spires; Parks; Commons; Boston Common; Public Garden; Massachusetts State House; Universities and colleges; Massachusetts Institute of Technology; New Old South Church; Central Congregational Church
  - Panorama of Beacon Hill and Back Bay, 1891; MS102.001.DO.00059; Unknown
    Massachusetts; Boston (Mass.); Beacon Hill (Mass.); Back Bay (Mass.); Beacon Street; Marlborough Street; Commonwealth Avenue; Newbury Street; Boylston Street; Buildings; Dwellings; Houses; Rivers; Charles River; Bridges; Harvard Bridge; Churches; Spires; Parks; Commons; Boston Common; Public Garden; Arlington Street Church; Central Congregational Church; First Baptist Church (Boston); New Old South Church
  - 13, 15 and 17 Hereford Street, 1979-03-29; MS102.001.DO.00060; Doran, Bill
    Massachusetts; Boston (Mass.); Back Bay (Mass.); Hereford Street; Marlborough Street; Buildings; Dwellings; Houses; Automobiles; People; Street-lighting
  - 63 Bay State Road, 1894; MS102.001.DO.00061; Unknown
    Massachusetts; Boston (Mass.); Back Bay (Mass.); Bay State Road; Buildings; Dwellings; Houses; Rivers; Charles River; Chapman, John H.; Frazer, Horace S.; Chapman and Frazer
  - 59 and 61 Bay State Road, 1893; MS102.001.DO.00062; Unknown
    Massachusetts; Boston (Mass.); Back Bay (Mass.); Bay State Road; Buildings; Dwellings; Houses; Wheelwright, Edmund M.; Haven, Parkman B.; Wheelwright and Haven
  - Houses along Beacon Street, 1860 -- 1880; MS102.001.DO.00066; Hawes, Josiah Johnson
    Massachusetts; Boston (Mass.); Beacon Street; Buildings; Dwellings; Houses; Hand-railing; Streets; Alleys
  - 84 and 85 Beacon Street, 1880; MS102.001.DO.00067; Hawes, Josiah Johnson
    Massachusetts; Boston (Mass.); Beacon Hill (Mass.); Beacon Street; Brimmer Street; Buildings; Dwellings; Houses; Commercial buildings; Businesses; Liveries; People; Horse-drawn vehicles; Carriages and carts; Horses; Signs and signboards; Street lights; Taylor, Charles H.; Garcelon, Alsom; Garcelon's Livery
  - 54 and 55 Beacon Street, 1840 -- 1880; MS102.001.DO.00069; Unknown
    Massachusetts; Boston (Mass.); Beacon Hill (Mass.); Beacon Street; Buildings; Dwellings; Houses; Hand-railing; Fences; Benjamin, Asher
  - Claflin Building at 18-20 Beacon Street, 1883 -- 1892; MS102.001.DO.00070; Unknown
    Massachusetts; Boston (Mass.); Beacon Hill (Mass.); Beacon Street; Buildings; Dwellings; Houses; Commercial buildings; Businesses; Social and civic buildings; Claflin Building; Signs and signboards; Clocks and watches; Scaffolding; Street lights; Murdock Parlor Grate Company
  - A team of horses pulling a wagon along Beacon Street, 1860 -- 1890; MS102.001.DO.00071; Unknown
    Massachusetts; Boston (Mass.); Beacon Street; Buildings; Dwellings; Houses; Hand-railing; People; Horse-drawn vehicles; Wagons
  - 39 and 40 Beacon Street, February, 1971-02-01; MS102.001.DO.00072; Unknown
    Massachusetts; Boston (Mass.); Beacon Hill (Mass.); Beacon Street; Buildings; Dwellings; Houses; Social and civic buildings; Associations, institutions, etc.; Women's City Club of Boston; Hand-railing; Flagpoles; Automobiles; Women's City Club of Boston
  - View from Boston Common of houses along Beacon Street, 1860 -- 1888; MS102.001.DO.00073; Clark, William T.
    Massachusetts; Boston (Mass.); Beacon Hill (Mass.); Beacon Street; Boston Common; Buildings; Dwellings; Houses; Parks; Commons; Boston Common; Hand-railing; Fences; Trees; Benches
  - Hancock House at 30 Beacon Street, 1830 -- 1860; MS102.001.DO.00074; Unknown
    Massachusetts; Boston (Mass.); Beacon Hill (Mass.); Beacon Street; Buildings; Dwellings; Houses; Public buildings; Government buildings; Massachusetts State House; Domes; Fences; Trees; Shrubs
  - English High and Public Latin School, Bedford Street, 1860., MS102.001.DO.00075; Unknown
    Massachusetts; Boston (Mass.); Bedford Street; School buildings; Fences; English High School and Public Latin School
  - Bedford Street, entrance of R.H. White & Co., n.d., MS102.001.DO.00076; Unknown
    Massachusetts; Boston (Mass.); Bedford Street; R.H. White & Co.
  - Jordan Marsh and Co. building, 69 Bedford Street, 1880; MS102.001.DO.00077; Unknown
    Massachusetts; Boston (Mass.); Bedford Street; Kingston Street; Buildings; Commercial buildings; Jordan Marsh & Company
  - Bedford Street at the corner of Lincoln and Summer Streets, 1900; MS102.001.DO.00078; Unknown
    Massachusetts; Boston (Mass.); Bedford Street; Lincoln Street; Buildings, stone; Horse-drawn vehicles; Bedford building; Commercial buildings; Signs and signboards; Friedman Brothers
  - Bedford building (detail) on Bedford Street, 1900; MS102.001.DO.00079; Unknown
    Massachusetts; Boston (Mass.); Bedford Street; Buildings, stone; Ironwork; Signs and signboards; Bedford building; Friedman Brothers
  - Bedford Street at Kingston Street, Ames building, 1900; MS102.001.DO.00080; Unknown
    Massachusetts; Boston (Mass.); Bedford Street; Kingston Street; Horse-drawn vehicles; Buildings, stone; Ames building
  - Building at Bedford and Chauncey Streets, 1900; MS102.001.DO.00081; Unknown